>> 演讲者 1: 您对 componentDidUpdate 的内容进行一些讨论
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: You talk a little bit
about when the componentDidUpdate
生命周期方法吗 ?
lifecycle methods?
>> Brian Holt: 当然，让我们快速处理所有错误信息。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Sure, let's get rid
of all the error stuff really quick.
在这里， >> Brian Holt:
So here,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Inside of
componentDidUpdate，因此 componentDidUpdate 将在以下情况下被调用 :
componentDidUpdate, so componentDidUpdate
is gonna get called when
道具改变了状态改变了对吧
props change a state change,
that's about it, right?
这与使用效果非常相似，对吧 ?
So it's very much similar to useEffect,
right?
因此， useEffect 会在其依赖关系更新的情况下运行。
So useEffect gets running
whatever its dependencies update.
componentDidUpdate 将每隔一段时间运行一次，
componentDidUpdate is gonna get run
every single time that a proper or
状态变化，对吧 ?
state changes, right?
这就是为什么我说如果这个国家发生了错误
So that's why I say,
if this state.hasError,
好，然后再将它设置为其他内容。
right, then set this to be something else.
现在，我可以这样说，因为只有一个国家。
Now, I could have just said this,
because this only has one piece of state.
但如果这个国家有更多的国家
But what happens later
if this has more state,
你想具体就像这样对吧
you wanna be specific,
like this reacts to this, right?
所以在这件案子里
So in this particular case,
这是对 componentDidCatch 的反应，对吧 ?
this is reacting to componentDidCatch
gets called, right?
或者不，对不起， getDerivedStateFromError，这会被调用，此更新
Or no, sorry, getDerivedStateFromError,
this gets called, this updates
hasError 为 true，然后将在此处调用 componentDidUpdate 。
the hasError to be true, which is then
going to call componentDidUpdate here.
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
>> 扬声器 1: 是，谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yes, thank you.
>> Brian Holt: 当然，好的问题。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Of course, good question.
>> 演讲者 3: 您是否可以实际讨论 getDerivedStateFromError?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Could you actually talk
about the getDerivedStateFromError?
那是怎么叫的
How does that get called?
React 如何知道要运行该功能?
How does React know to run that function?
>> Brian Holt: 对不起，这被称为
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Sorry, this gets called
只要里面有错误就行了吧
whenever there's an error inside of it,
right?
因为它是静态方法，可以在类上调用，而不是在
And so because it's a static method,
it can call it on the class and not on
这并不是你真正在乎的事情。
the instance, not that that's really a
thing that you really care too much about.
但它会用这个方法
But what it'll do is
it'll call this method,
它会传入， >> 扬声器 3:
it'll pass in,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Is that
因为命名约定要通知它吗
because of the naming convention
that it knows to call it?
> > Brian Holt: 是，我想，我不- >> 演讲者 3: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yes, I guess, I don't-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay.
>> Brian Holt: 是的，必须这样做。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, so
it has to be called this.
在这个意义上是一个生命周期的方法，对吧 ?
This is a lifecycle method in that sense,
right?
>> 演讲者 3: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay.
> > Brian Holt: 就像我们一样，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Just like we had,
what was the-
>> 扬声器 3: 在轮播上 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: On carousel?
>> Brian Holt: 对，在 carousel 上，也有 getDerivedStateFromProps。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, on the carousel
one as well, getDerivedStateFromProps.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，它会在此处传递错误。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So yeah,
it'll pass in the error here.
对我们来说我们知道现在有个错误所以我们要更新那个状态
For us, we just know there's an error now,
so we're gonna update that state and
那么它就会重新呈现这个新状态
then it's going to re-render
with that new state.
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
太酷了
Cool.
>> 扬声器 4: 如果生产中存在未处理的错误，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: If there's an error
in production that's not handled,
React 执行什么操作 ?
what does React do?
>> Brian Holt: 未安装。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It unmounts.
>> 演讲者 4: 对。 > > Brian Holt: 是的，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Right.
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah,
只是把整个事情都从 DOM中取出来
it just takes the entire
thing out of the DOM.
所以很多公司都有一个顶级的错误处理程序，
So a lot of companies will just have
one top level error handler, and
来处理整个应用
that'll handle the entire app.
但是，您还可以有多个级别的可能，您的页脚有很多错误。
But you can also have multiple levels of
maybe your footer has a lot of errors.
也许你不该有那页脚
Maybe you shouldn't have that footer.
但也许是这样
But maybe it does, right,
但你可以专门为你的脚做的对吧
but then you could have one
specifically for your footer, right.
是吗马克
Yeah, Mark?
>> 标记: 是否可以将边界与功能挂钩配合使用 ?
&gt;&gt; Mark: Can error boundaries
be used with functional hooks?
>> Brian Holt: 否，因为 getDerivedStatesFromErrors，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: No,
because getDerivedStatesFromErrors,
有一个可以捕捉到这个物质的末端组件。
there is end component to catch for
that matter.
这与挂钩没有同等的功能。
There is no equivalent for
these with hooks.
所以这个你实际上要用分类组件。
So this one you actually
have to use class component.
>> 标记: 当前?
&gt;&gt; Mark: Currently?
>> Brian Holt: 目前没有计划来解决该问题，但
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Currently,
there's no plans to fix that, but
这不是说不会有计划的
that isn't to say that,
there won't be plans.
但是，目前还没有办法用钩子。
But yeah, currently there's
no way to do it with hooks.
>> Mark: 那么您可以使用它来合并使用挂钩的组件吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Mark: So could you use it to wrap
a component that's using hooks?
>> Brian Holt: 对，是的，因为this.propss.子代可能是什么，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right, yeah, because
this.props.children can be anything,
对吧 ?
right?
它对儿童所做的任何事情都没有任何意见。
It has no opinion on whatever
its children are gonna be doing.